<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Skin Detector</string>
    <string name="skin_text">Please select proper skin affected image from gallery otherwise it will show wrong prediction.</string>
    <string name="skin_hint">Skin disease result will show here..</string>
    <string name="actinic_keratosis">Sun safety is necessary to help prevent development and recurrence of actinic keratosis patches and spots.\nTake these steps to protect your skin from the sun: \n

        - <b>Limit your time in the sun.</b> Especially avoid time in the sun between 10 a.m. and 2 p.m. And avoid staying in the sun so long that you get a sunburn or a suntan.
        - <b>Use sunscreen.</b> Before spending time outdoors, even on cloud days, apply a broad-spectrum water-resistant sunscreen with a sun protection factor (SPF) of at least 30, as the American Academy of Dermatology recommends.\n\nUse sunscreen on all exposed skin, and use lip balm with sunscreen on your lips. Apply sunscreen at least 15 minutes before going outside and reapply it every two hours — or more often if you\'re swimming or perspiring.\n\nSunscreen is not recommended for babies under 6 months. Rather, keep them out of the sun if possible, or protect them with shade, hats, and clothing that covers the arms and legs.
        - <b>Cover up.</b> For extra protection from the sun, wear tightly woven clothing that covers your arms and legs. Also wear a broad-brimmed hat, which provides more protection than does a baseball cap or golf visor.
        - <b>Avoid tanning beds.</b> The UV exposure from a tanning bed can cause just as much skin damage as a tan acquired from the sun.
        - <b>Check your skin regularly and report changes to your doctor.</b> Examine your skin regularly, looking for the development of new skin growths or changes in existing moles, freckles, bumps and birthmarks. With the help of mirrors, check your face, neck, ears and scalp. Examine the tops and undersides of your arms and hands.</string>
    <string name="basal_cell">To reduce your risk of basal cell carcinoma you can:\n\n
        - <b>Avoid the sun during the middle of the day.</b> In many places, the sun\'s rays are strongest between about 10 a.m. and 4 p.m. Schedule outdoor activities for other times of the day, even during winter or when the sky is cloudy. \n\n<b>Wear sunscreen year-round.</b> Use a broad-spectrum sunscreen with an SPF of at least 30, even on cloudy days. Apply sunscreen generously, and reapply every two hours — or more often if you\'re swimming or perspiring. \n\n<b>Wear protective clothing.</b> Cover your skin with dark, tightly woven clothing that covers your arms and legs, and a broad-brimmed hat, which provides more protection than does a baseball cap or visor.  \nSome companies also sell protective clothing. A dermatologist can recommend an appropriate brand. Don\'t forget sunglasses. Look for those that block both types of UV radiation — UVA and UVB rays.  \n\n<b>Avoid tanning beds.</b> Tanning beds emit UV rays and can increase your risk of skin cancer. \n\n<b>Check your skin regularly and report changes to your doctor.</b> Examine your skin often for new skin growths or changes in existing moles, freckles, bumps and birthmarks. With the help of mirrors, check your face, neck, ears and scalp.  \nExamine your chest and trunk and the tops and undersides of your arms and hands. Examine both the front and the back of your legs and your feet, including the soles and the spaces between your toes. Also check your genital area and between your buttocks.</string>
    <string name="derma_text">A doctor may wish to rule out conditions that can look similar to dermatofibromas. Some of the possible diagnoses for growths that may, in rare cases, resembleTrusted Source dermatofibromas are:  \n -hypertrophic scarring or keloid \n -malignant melanoma \n -squamous cell carcinoma \n -basal cell carcinoma \n -Spitz nevus \n -blue nevus \n\nA rare skin cancer called dermatofibrosarcoma protuberans also initially resemblesTrusted Source a dermatofibroma.  \nDue to this, a qualified doctor should always make the diagnosis.</string>
    <string name="melanoma_text">You can reduce your risk of melanoma and other types of skin cancer if you:  \n<b>Avoid the sun during the middle of the day.</b> For many people in North America, the sun\'s rays are strongest between about 10 a.m. and 4 p.m. Schedule outdoor activities for other times of the day, even in winter or when the sky is cloudy.  You absorb UV radiation year-round, and clouds offer little protection from damaging rays. Avoiding the sun at its strongest helps you avoid the sunburns and suntans that cause skin damage and increase your risk of developing skin cancer. Sun exposure accumulated over time also may cause skin cancer.  \n\n<b>Wear sunscreen year-round.</b> Use a broad-spectrum sunscreen with an SPF of at least 30, even on cloudy days. Apply sunscreen generously, and reapply every two hours — or more often if you\'re swimming or perspiring. \n\n<b>Wear protective clothing.</b> Cover your skin with dark, tightly woven clothing that covers your arms and legs, and a broad-brimmed hat, which provides more protection than does a baseball cap or visor.  Some companies also sell protective clothing. A dermatologist can recommend an appropriate brand. Don\'t forget sunglasses. Look for those that block both types of UV radiation — UVA and UVB rays.</string>
    <string name="squ_cell">To reduce your risk of squamous cell carcinom you can:\n\n
        - <b>Avoid the sun during the middle of the day.</b> In many places, the sun\'s rays are strongest between about 10 a.m. and 4 p.m. Schedule outdoor activities for other times of the day, even during winter or when the sky is cloudy. \n\n<b>Wear sunscreen year-round.</b> Use a broad-spectrum sunscreen with an SPF of at least 30, even on cloudy days. Apply sunscreen generously, and reapply every two hours — or more often if you\'re swimming or perspiring. \n\n<b>Wear protective clothing.</b> Cover your skin with dark, tightly woven clothing that covers your arms and legs, and a broad-brimmed hat, which provides more protection than does a baseball cap or visor.  \nSome companies also sell protective clothing. A dermatologist can recommend an appropriate brand. Don\'t forget sunglasses. Look for those that block both types of UV radiation — UVA and UVB rays.  \n\n<b>Avoid tanning beds.</b> Tanning beds emit UV rays and can increase your risk of skin cancer. \n\n<b>Check your skin regularly and report changes to your doctor.</b> Examine your skin often for new skin growths or changes in existing moles, freckles, bumps and birthmarks. With the help of mirrors, check your face, neck, ears and scalp.  \nExamine your chest and trunk and the tops and undersides of your arms and hands. Examine both the front and the back of your legs and your feet, including the soles and the spaces between your toes. Also check your genital area and between your buttocks.</string>
    <string name="vas_cell">To reduce your risk of vascular lesion you can:\n\n
        - <b>Avoid the sun during the middle of the day.</b> In many places, the sun\'s rays are strongest between about 10 a.m. and 4 p.m. Schedule outdoor activities for other times of the day, even during winter or when the sky is cloudy. \n\n<b>Wear sunscreen year-round.</b> Use a broad-spectrum sunscreen with an SPF of at least 30, even on cloudy days. Apply sunscreen generously, and reapply every two hours — or more often if you\'re swimming or perspiring. \n\n<b>Wear protective clothing.</b> Cover your skin with dark, tightly woven clothing that covers your arms and legs, and a broad-brimmed hat, which provides more protection than does a baseball cap or visor.  \nSome companies also sell protective clothing. A dermatologist can recommend an appropriate brand. Don\'t forget sunglasses. Look for those that block both types of UV radiation — UVA and UVB rays.  \n\n<b>Avoid tanning beds.</b> Tanning beds emit UV rays and can increase your risk of skin cancer. \n\n<b>Check your skin regularly and report changes to your doctor.</b> Examine your skin often for new skin growths or changes in existing moles, freckles, bumps and birthmarks. With the help of mirrors, check your face, neck, ears and scalp.  \nExamine your chest and trunk and the tops and undersides of your arms and hands. Examine both the front and the back of your legs and your feet, including the soles and the spaces between your toes. Also check your genital area and between your buttocks.</string>
    <string name="select_image">Select Image</string>
    <string name="predict_text">Prediction</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="actinic_Prevention">How to prevent actinic keratosis?</string>
    <string name="ac_prevent1">Applying sunscreen every day, even in cloudy weather or during winter, and re-applying often — at least every two hours. Use a broad-spectrum sunscreen with at least 30 sun protection factor (SPF) that blocks both UVA and UVB light.</string>
    <string name="ac_prevent2">Avoiding sun exposure when UV light is most intense, between 10 a.m. and 2 p.m.</string>
    <string name="ac_prevent3">Avoiding tanning salons, sun lamps and tanning beds.</string>
    <string name="ac_prevent4">Wearing sun-safe clothing, such as long-sleeved shirts, long pants and hats.</string>
    <string name="actinic_management">How is actinic keratosis treated?</string>
    <string name="ac_management">To remove actinic keratosis, your provider may use:</string>
    <string name="ac_manage1"><b>Chemical peels:</b> A chemical peel is like a medical-grade face mask. Your healthcare provider applies the peel during an office visit. The chemicals in the treatment safely destroy unwanted patches in your top layer of skin.</string>
    <string name="ac_manage2"><b>Cryotherapy:</b> If you have one or two AKs, your provider may use cryotherapy. During this treatment, your provider uses a cold substance such as liquid nitrogen to freeze skin growths.</string>
    <string name="ac_manage3"><b>Excision:</b> During this treatment, your healthcare provider first numbs the skin around your AK. Your provider then scrapes away or cuts out the AKs and stitches the area back together.</string>
    <string name="ac_manage4"><b>Photodynamic therapy:</b> If you have multiple AKs or AKs that return after treatment, your provider may recommend photodynamic therapy.</string>
    <string name="basal_Prevention">How to prevent Basal Cell Carcinoma?</string>
    <string name="basal_prevent">To reduce your risk of basal cell carcinoma you can:</string>
    <string name="basal_prevent1">Avoid the sun during the middle of the day. In many places, the sun\'s rays are strongest between about 10 a.m. and 4 p.m.</string>
    <string name="basal_prevent2">Wear sunscreen year-round. Use a broad-spectrum sunscreen with an SPF of at least 30, even on cloudy days.</string>
    <string name="basal_prevent3">Wear protective clothing. Cover your skin with dark, tightly woven clothing that covers your arms and legs, and a broad-brimmed hat, which provides more protection than does a baseball cap or visor.</string>
    <string name="basal_prevent4">Avoid tanning beds. Tanning beds emit UV rays and can increase your risk of skin cancer.</string>
    <string name="basal_management">What are the treatments for basal cell carcinoma (BCC)?</string>
    <string name="basal_manage">The choice of treatment depends on many things, including patient health and age, the location of the tumor, and the extent and type of the cancer. Treatment may occur in many ways:</string>
    <string name="basal_manage1">Scratching off with a curette, an instrument that may end in a ring or a spoon, and then burning with a special electric needle. This method is called electrodessication and curettage.</string>
    <string name="basal_manage2">"Mohs surgery: This is a specialized technique. The doctor first removes the visible cancer and then begins cutting around the edges. "</string>
    <string name="basal_manage3">Applying chemotherapy medication to the skin</string>
    <string name="basal_manage4">Using blue light and a light-sensitive agent applied to the skin (photodynamic therapy or PDT)</string>
    <string name="derma_Prevention">How to prevent dermatofibroma?</string>
    <string name="derma_prevent1">Researchers don\’t currently know exactly why the dermatofibromas occur in some people.\n\nBecause the cause is unknown, there is no sure way to prevent dermatofibromas from developing.</string>
    <string name="derma_management">How is dermatofibroma treated?</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management">Typically, dermatofibromas are chronic and don\’t spontaneously resolve on their own. Because they are harmless, treatment is usually solely for cosmetic reasons.\n\nTreatment options for dermatofibromas include:</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management1">freezing (with liquid nitrogen)</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management2">localized corticosteroid injection</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management3">laser therapy</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management4">shaving the top to flatten the growth</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management5">These therapies may not be completely successful at removing a dermatofibroma because the tissue may reaccumulate within the lesion until it returns to its size before therapy.</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management6">A dermatofibroma can be completely removed with a wide surgical excision, but there is also a high likelihood of scar formation that may be considered more unsightly than the dermatofibroma itself.</string>
    <string name="dermaa_management7"><u>Never attempt removal of a growth at home. This can lead to infection, scarring, and excess bleeding.</u></string>
    <string name="melanoma_Prevention">How to prevent Melanoma?</string>
    <string name="melanoma_management">How is Melanoma treated?</string>
    <string name="melanoma_prevent1">You can reduce your risk of melanoma and other types of skin cancer if you:</string>
    <string name="mela_management">If melanoma has spread beyond the skin, treatment options may include:</string>
    <string name="mela_management1"><b>Surgery to remove affected lymph nodes.</b> If melanoma has spread to nearby lymph nodes, your surgeon may remove the affected nodes.</string>
    <string name="mela_management2"><b>Immunotherapy.</b> Immunotherapy is a drug treatment that helps your immune system to fight cancer.</string>
    <string name="mela_management3"><b>Targeted therapy.</b> Targeted drug treatments focus on specific weaknesses present within cancer cells.</string>
    <string name="mela_management4"><b>Radiation therapy.</b> This treatment uses high-powered energy beams, such as X-rays and protons, to kill cancer cells.</string>
    <string name="mela_management5"><b>Chemotherapy:</b> Chemotherapy uses drugs to kill cancer cells. Chemotherapy can be given intravenously, in pill form or both so that it travels throughout your body.</string>
    <string name="nevus_Prevention">How to prevent Nevus?</string>
    <string name="nevus_management">How is Nevus treated?</string>
    <string name="nevus_prevent1">You can reduce your risk of nevus and other types of skin cancer if you:</string>
    <string name="nevuss_management">If nevus has spread beyond the skin, treatment options may include:</string>
    <string name="sebo_Prevention">How to prevent Seborrheic Keratosis?</string>
    <string name="sebo_prevent1">There is no way to completely prevent the development of seborrheic keratoses. However, if you know you\’re at risk or you frequently develop these growths, working with a dermatologist means you can limit the impact this skin condition has on your life.</string>
    <string name="sebo_management">How is seborrheic keratosis treated?</string>
    <string name="seborr_management">You should always have new skin growths clinically diagnosed to make sure they aren\’t cancerous. Different kinds of skin growths can be hard to tell apart from each other. If your healthcare provider is in any doubt about your growth, they might want to remove it for biopsy.</string>
    <string name="seborr_management1">If it is clearly a seborrheic keratosis, it won\’t require any treatment. But you might want to have it removed if it becomes itchy or irritated or you don\’t like the look of it. Your healthcare provider can remove it for you in the office using one of several common methods.</string>
    <string name="pigmented_Prevention">How to prevent Pigmented Benign Keratosis?</string>
    <string name="pigmented_prevent1">There is no way to completely prevent the development of Pigmented Benign Keratosis. However, if you know you\’re at risk or you frequently develop these growths, working with a dermatologist means you can limit the impact this skin condition has on your life.</string>
    <string name="pigmented_management">How is Pigmented Benign Keratosis treated?</string>
    <string name="pigmented_management1">If it is clearly a Pigmented Benign Keratosis, it won\’t require any treatment. But you might want to have it removed if it becomes itchy or irritated or you don\’t like the look of it. Your healthcare provider can remove it for you in the office using one of several common methods.</string>
    <string name="squa_Prevention">How to prevent Squamous cell carcinoma?</string>
    <string name="squa_management">How is Squamous cell carcinoma treated?</string>
    <string name="squaa_management"><b><u>Treatments for very small skin cancers</u></b>\n\nIf your skin cancer is very small and has a low risk of spreading, you might consider less invasive treatments, including:</string>
    <string name="squaa_management1"><b>Curettage and electrodessication (C and E).</b> C and E treatment involves removing the surface of the skin cancer with a scraping instrument (curet) and then searing the base of the cancer with an electric needle.</string>
    <string name="squaa_management2"><b>Laser therapy.</b> An intense beam of light vaporizes growths, usually with little damage to surrounding tissue and with a reduced risk of bleeding, swelling and scarring.</string>
    <string name="squaa_management3"><b>Freezing.</b> This treatment involves freezing cancer cells with liquid nitrogen (cryosurgery). It may be an option for treating superficial skin lesions.</string>
    <string name="squaa_management4"><b>Photodynamic therapy.</b> Photodynamic therapy combines photosensitizing drugs and light to treat superficial skin cancers. During photodynamic therapy, a liquid drug that makes the cancer cells sensitive to light is applied to the skin. Later, a light that destroys the skin cancer cells is shined on the area.</string>
    <string name="squaam_management"><b><u>Treatments for larger skin cancers</u></b>\n\nMore invasive treatments might be recommended for larger squamous cell carcinomas and those that extend deeper into the skin. Options might include:</string>
    <string name="squaam_management1"><b>Simple excision.</b> In this procedure, your doctor cuts out the cancerous tissue and a surrounding margin of healthy skin.</string>
    <string name="squaam_management2"><b>Mohs surgery.</b> During Mohs surgery, your doctor removes the cancer layer by layer, examining each layer under the microscope until no abnormal cells remain.</string>
    <string name="squaam_management3"><b>Radiation therapy.</b> Radiation therapy uses high-energy beams, such as X-rays and protons, to kill cancer cells.</string>
    <string name="squaamo_management"><b><u>Treatments for skin cancer that spreads beyond the skin</u></b>\n\nWhen squamous cell carcinoma spreads to other parts of the body, drug treatments might be recommended, including:</string>
    <string name="squaamo_management1"><b>Chemotherapy.</b> Chemotherapy uses powerful drugs to kill cancer cells. If squamous cell carcinoma spreads to the lymph nodes or other parts of the body, chemotherapy can be used alone or in combination with other treatments, such as targeted drug therapy and radiation therapy.</string>
    <string name="squaamo_management2"><b>Targeted drug therapy.</b> Targeted drug treatments focus on specific weaknesses present within cancer cells.</string>
    <string name="squaamo_management3"><b>Immunotherapy.</b> Immunotherapy is a drug treatment that helps your immune system to fight cancer. Your body\'s disease-fighting immune system might not attack cancer because the cancer cells produce proteins that blind the immune system cells.</string>
    <string name="vascular_management">How is vascular lesion treated?</string>
    <string name="vas_management">There are different types of treatment for childhood vascular tumors.</string>
    <string name="vas_management1">Children with childhood vascular tumors should have their treatment planned by a team of health care providers who are experts in treating cancer in children.</string>
    <string name="vas_management2">Twelve types of standard treatment are used:\n - Beta-blocker therapy\n - Surgery\n - Photocoagulation\n - Cryotherapy\n - Embolization\n - Chemotherapy\n - Sclerotherapy\n -Radiation therapy\n - Targeted therapy\n - Immuno therapy\n - Other drug therapy</string>
    <string name="Prevention">How to prevent Malignant lung Cancer?</string>
    <string name="m_prevent1">Not all Skin cancers can be prevented. But there are things you can do that might lower your risk.</string>
    <string name="m_prevent2"><b>Stay away from tobacco</b> The best way to reduce your risk of lung cancer is not to smoke and to avoid breathing in other people\’s smoke. If you stop smoking before a cancer develops, your damaged lung tissue gradually starts to repair itself. No matter what your age or how long you\’ve smoked, quitting may lower your risk of lung cancer and help you live longer.</string>
    <string name="m_prevent3"><b>Avoid radon exposure</b> Radon is an important cause of lung cancer. You can reduce your exposure to radon by having your home tested and treated, if needed.</string>
    <string name="m_prevent4"><b>Avoid or limit exposure to cancer-causing agents</b> Avoiding exposure to known cancer-causing agents, in the workplace and elsewhere, may also be helpful. When people work where these exposures are common, they should be kept to a minimum.</string>
    <string name="m_prevent5"><b>Eat a healthy diet</b> A healthy diet with lots of fruits and vegetables may also help reduce your risk of lung cancer. Some evidence suggests that a diet high in fruits and vegetables may help protect people who smoke and those who don\'t against lung cancer. But any positive effect of fruits and vegetables on lung cancer risk would be much less than the increased risk from smoking.</string>

</resources>